Jinbe came to help?!
جينبي أنقذكم؟
Yeah, I was surprised too.
أجل، لقد فاجأني أيضًا
That's a relief. So Nami-san is okay...
هذا مطمئن، إذًا نامي-سان بخير
But now, we need to figure out how to meet up with them.
ولكن المشكلة تكمن في كيفية الالتقاء بهم الآن
Once they hear you're coming back, I'm sure they'll be happy.
عندما يعلمون بأنّك عُدت إلينا مجدّدًا، ستغمرهم السعادة جميعًا
Goodbye!
الوداع
Sorry...
...أعتذر
we should never have done this!
ما كان يجدر بنا التدخل
I'm too ashamed to face Nami-san...
أنا مُحرج جدًّا من مقابلة نامي-سان بعد ما فعلته فعلته
Nami and the others were so worried about you.
نامي والآخرين قلقين عليك بغض النظر عمّا فعلته
And yet, I put them through this terrifying ordeal...
مع ذلك، جعلتهم يشعرون بالخوف عليّ
Oh, the rain is stopping.
ماذا؟ المطر يتوقّف
I found it!
عثرت عليها
You sure?! Chobro!
حقًّا يا تشونيكي؟
Do you think they can hear us through this piece of glass?
أتظنون أنّهما سيكونان قادرين على سماعنا عبر هذه القطعة الصغيرة من المرآة؟
The last mirror piece I used to talk to you guys broke on the head of that tree monster, Kingbaum.
المرآة التي تحدثت إليكم عبرها في آخر مرة تحطمت فوق رأس ذاك الوحش الشجرة المدعو كينغبوم
It broke!
تحطمت
So...
...لذا
There should be at least a piece of glass that connects to this one.
لا بدّ أن يكون هناك بعض القطع المتناثرة على الأقل
Hey! Luffy!
يا لوفي
Luffy!
لوفي
Are you there, Luffy?!
هل أنت هنا يا لوفي؟
Is that...?
أهذا...؟
It's Chopper!
إنّه صوت تشوبر
Answer me if you're there!
أجبني إن كنت هناك
Chopper!
تشوبر
Luffy!
لوفي
Luffy! Can you hear me?!
لوفي، هل تسمعني؟
Here it is!
ها هو
This is it! It's a piece of glass!
هذه هي، إنّها قطعة من المرآة
Can you hear me?!
هل تستطيع سماعي؟
Why is his voice coming out of a mirror?
لماذا صوته يصدر من المرآة؟
It's a long story, but Chopper and the others are in a mirror dimension.
إنّها قصة طويلة، ولكن باختصار تشوبر والآخرين داخل المرآة
Are you okay, Chopper?
هل أنتم بخير يا تشوبر؟
Oh, Luffy! Thank goodness! You're really there!
لوفي، هذا مطمئن، كنتَ حقًّا هناك
Luffy! Is Sanji-kun there too?!
لوفي، هل سانجي معك أيضًا؟
Yeah, he's here!
أجل، إنّه هنا
Sanji-san, I'm glad that you're okay.
إني سعيدٌ أنّك بخير يا سانجي-سان
How are you guys?
ماذا عنكم؟
We saved everybody from inside the mirror, Luffy!
تمكّنا من إنقاذ الجميع من داخل المرآيا يا لوفي
Brook even got copies of the poneglyphs!
وبروك تمكّن من نسخ أحجار البونغليف
Really?!
حقًّا؟
I'm impressed with you guys!
كما هو متوقع منكم يا رفاق
Y-Your compliment doesn't make me happy, you fool!
لن أفرح بمديحك أيها الوغد
You fool!
أيها الوغد
You silly little goose!
أيها المغفل السخيف
Luffy, it's good that Sanji's there, but did you two come to an agreement?
لوفي، لمن الجيّد أن سانجي معك ولكن هل قمتما بتسوية الأمر بينكما؟
Sanji isn't... coming back yet.
سانجي ليس عائدًا بعد
What?!
ماذا؟
Listen, everyone.
اسمعوا يا رفاق
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party and the wedding.
سندمّر حفلة الشاي لبيغ مام خلال مراسم الزفاف
And we're gonna save Sanji's family!
وسننقذ عائلة سانجي من الخطر المُحدق بهم
And then, Sanji will leave with us!
وبعد ذلك، سانجي سيعود إلينا
B... Big...
بـ-بيغ
Luffy! She's an emperor!
لوفي، إنّها إمبراطورة
I don't want to risk everyone's... I mean, Nami-san's life over my own personal issues!
لا أريد لأنانيتي أن تعرّض حياة الجميع للخطر أقصد حياة نامي-سان بالأخص
So...
...لذا
Yay!
مرحى
Damn you!
ما بالك يا هذا؟
I heard you and Luffy got into a big fight, so I was worried, you idiot!
كنتُ قلقًا عليك عندما سمعت بأنّك خضت قتالًا عنيفًا مع لوفي أيها الأحمق
I'm so relieved! Really, you idiot!
هذا مطمئن، كنتُ قلقة عليك حقًّا أيها الأحمق
You big idiot!
أيها المغفل
If we do that, then Sanji-kun will leave with us, right, Luffy?!
إذًا هذا يعني أنّ سانجي سيعود إلينا بعدما نقوم بذلك يا لوفي؟
Nami-san... I...
...نامي-سان، عذرًا
Oh, Sanji-kun.
صحيح، سانجي-كن
For scaring me like you did...
...كونك جعلت الرعب يدبّ في قلبي
I will never forgive you!
فلن أسامحك أبدًا
Nami...
نامي
But we can talk about that later. The tea party is soon.
ولكن دعنا ننسى هذا الأمر حاليًّا فحفلة الشاي لم يتبقّ لها سوى القليل
I'm gonna help bring you back no matter what, Sanji-kun!
أنا سأستعيدك مهما كلّف الثمن يا سانجي-كن
What?! Are you proposing to me, Nami-san ?!
ضربة
Thump!
أيعتبر هذا طلب زواج يا نامي-سان؟
I don't know why, but I think you're fine now.
حسنًا، أنا واثق بأنّك بخير الآن
Alright, Luffy, we know what we need to do now.
حسنًا يا لوفي، ذلك يوضّح ما يجب بنا القيام به
Yeah.
أجل
By the way, Sanji's sister saved my life.
بالمناسبة، لقد أنقذت أُخت سانجي حياتي
So I wanna save them all.
لذا يجب أن ننقذها
Yes, let's save them all.
أجل، سننقذها
But it will not be easy.
ولكن ذلك لن يكون سهلًا
Even though we're not aiming to take Big Mom down,
رغم أننا لا ننوي هزيمة بيغ مام بحد ذاتها
she always looks forward to her tea parties.
إلّا أنّها تتطلّع شوقًا لحفلات الشاي الخاصة بها
By crashing it, we'll unleash the wrath of an emperor.
لذا لو أفسدنا حفلتها، سنجعل أحد الأباطرة يستشيط غضبًا علينا
On top of that, while I'm sure you've faced a number of Big Mom's ministers,
وعلاوة على ذلك، أظنكم واجهتم العديد من تابعيها في الجزيرة
they are merely the tip of the iceberg of her forces.
لكن أولئك كانوا جزءًا بسيطًا من طاقم قراصنة بيغ مام
The figures attending the tea party will be even more fearsome.
سيحضر لحفلة الشاي العديد من الأفراد الأكثر قوةً ورتبةً منهم
Not to mention her invited guests from around the world, the kingpins of the underworld.
ناهيك عن أباطرة العالم السفلي الذين تمّت دعوتهم من شتّى أنحاء العالم
We, on the other hand...
...في المقابل، هناك فقط
Have 10 people in total.
عشرة منّا
Hey! We're not part of this!
أنت، لا تعدّنا ضمنكم
Don't round up! There are only eight of you!
لا تتلاعب بالأرقام، هنالك ثمانية منكم فقط
I hope they slaughter you!
آمل أن يقتلوكم
Luffy.
لوفي
I've already told everyone here,
ثمّة أمر أودّ إخبارك به، وقد أخبرت به الجميع هنا مسبقًا
Have you ever heard of Capone "Gang" Bege?
أنت تعرف كابوني غانغ بيجي، صحيح؟
Yeah, he's the guy who took Sanji away.
أجل، إنّه الشخص الذي خطف سانجي
He's one of the Worst Generation, with a name as infamous as yours.
إنّه أحد أفراد الجيل الأسوأ مثلك
He hails from the West Blue, where there are five powerful mafia familes.
...ثمة خمس عوائل مافيا كُبرى في موطنه الأزرق الغربي
They control the underworld.
تُبسط سيطرتها على عالم الجريمة هناك
They are known as the Five Families of the West, and one of those bosses,
عائلات المافيا الخمس للأزرق الغربي ...أحد قادتها الخمس كان
is "Gang" Bege.
غانغ بيجي
He was given his "Gang" epithet when he was young. He used to be a notorious hitman.
عصابة
A hitman...
...قاتل مأجور
I heard he was a sick young man who cut the heads off helpless creatures
سمعت أنّه كان شابًّا يعشق أذية الحيوانات البريئة
and took joy watching them in the throes of death.
ويتلذذ برؤية أجسادهم تتجرّع أشد أنواع الألم وتحتضر
What kind of awful person would...?
ما مدى فظاعة ذلك الشخص؟
Now imagine that happening to an organization.
وقد كان يفعل الأمر ذاته مع عوائل المافيا
How does it taste?
ما رأيك بمذاقه؟
I wish it were more bitter.
أتمنى لو كان أكثر مرارة
Then, how about this?
إذًا ما رأيك بهذا؟
Boss!
أيها الزعيم
You little...
أيها الحقير
The lead tastes bitter, doesn't it?
مذاق الرصاص أكثر مرارة، أليس كذلك؟
In his days as a young gangster, he only killed the leaders of criminal organizations.
في أيام شبابه، كان يستهدف زعماء العالم السفلي ويقتلهم
And when he became the leader of his own family, he continued to only kill rival bosses.
وحتّى بعدما أصبح زعيم عائلته، ما زال يستهدف زعماء العوائل المنافسة
Bege?
بيجي؟
Don't resist.
لا تقاوم
What? Are you betraying me?!
ماذا؟ هل قمت بخيانتي؟
You're outnumbered!
أنت مخطئ
Bege!
بيجي
But Bege...
...لكن بيجي
never showed interest in his enemy's position or territory.
لم يبدِ اهتمامًا بمنصب العدو أو احتلال أراضيه
He merely took their valuables and left.
كان يأخذ المال والسلع فقط
Afterward, he would enjoy watching the violent power struggles within the groups
ثم بدأ يستمتع بمشاهدة التناحر الدامي الذي صنعه بيده بين العصابات
and the confusion of their allied syndicates.
بعدما كان بينهم تعاون سري من أجل مصالحهم المشتركة
He is truly a tasteless man.
إنّه حقًّا شخص مثير للاشمئزاز
But in this world, what goes around comes around.
ولكن كما يقولون، لكل فعل ردة فعل
He is now targeted constantly by those seeking vengeance.
فقد بدأ أولئك الذين طالتهم مكائده باستهدافه والترصد له بُغية الانتقام
However,
...ومع ذلك
Bege treats that like a game. He uses his iron fortress to fight them off,
كان ذلك مجرّد لعب ومرح لبيجي فهو يملك حصنًا منيعًا بانتظارهم
and mocks the weakness of his enemies.
جعلهم يجرّون أذيال الهزيمة وسط ضحكاته
When he got tired of being on land, he went out to sea and carried on his own ways.
وحتّى بعد أن أصابه الملل من البقاء على اليابسة شدّ الرحال إلى البحار منتهجًا نفس الأسلوب
Boss!
أيها الزعيم
Who did this?! Damn!
من فعل هذا؟ سحقًا
He's made his name by taking out pirate captains. Only the pirate captains.
اكتسب سمعةً سيئة من خلال قتل قادة القراصنة المشهورين فقط دون غيرهم
Even at sea, he is plagued by enemies seeking revenge...
بالنسبة لشخصٍ ما زال مستهدفًا حتّى في البحر من قبل الأعداء الذين يسعون للانتقام
So, working for an emperor is his perfect safe haven.
فالعمل تحت وطأة أحد الأباطرة هو الملاذ الآمن المثالي
That's why he decided to ally with Big Mom.
لهذا قرّر بيجي أن يكون تابعًا لبيغ مام
Because Big Mom thought highly of his sharpened sense of vigilance and incredible defensive ability,
وبعد اعترافها بشدة حذره وقدراته الدفاعية الهائلة
he was granted the title of rook just before the upcoming tea party,
نال لقب قطعة «القلعة» لحفلة الشاي المُقبلة
and placed in charge of security for the entire event.
وقد أسندت إليه مسؤولية تأمين هذا الحدث بأكمله
Why are you telling us this now, Jinbe?
لماذا تخبرنا بهذا الآن يا جينبي؟
If they are the security guards, nobody can stop them from achieving their goal.
إن كان حرّاس الأمن بصفنا، فلا أحد يمكنه أن يقف في طريقنا
Huh?
ماذا؟
The main event of this tea party is the wedding.
الحدث الرئيسي لحفلة الشاي هو الزفاف
As you are now aware, Big Mom intends to slaughter the Vinsmokes during the ceremony,
وكما تعلمون، بيغ مام تنوي قتل جميع أفراد فينسموك أثناء مراسمه
and then acquire the remnants of Germa for herself.
كي تستحوذ على قوة جيرما
But meanwhile, behind her back, Bege has his own plan to take Big Mom's head.
وسط كل هذا، بيجي سيقوم باغتيال بيغ مام
What?!
ماذا؟
What the hell is going on?! Everyone is planning their own conspiracies!
ما هذا؟ جلّ ما يحدث عبارة عن دوامة من المؤامرات
Luffy, I'm sure you remember that Pekoms was the one who guided you here.
لوفي، بيكومز الذي قادكم جميعًا إلى هذه الجزيرة
He was kidnapped by Bege,
لقد تمّ خطفه من قبل بيجي وعصابته
and they tried to get him to cooperate with their plan.
وعرضوا عليه أن يكون شريكًا في مكيدتهم
Pekoms... So that's where he went...
بيكومز... هذا ما حدث له إذًا
Pekoms is loyal, so he refused. In order to keep him quiet, Bege shot him off a cliff into a swarm of sharks.
بما أنّ بيكومز مُخلص للغاية أسقطه بيجي في البحر المكتظ بأسماك القرش كي يضمن إسكاته
What?!
ماذا؟
But...
...لكن
my companions were watching and saved him just in time.
رفاقي لاحظوا ذلك وأنقذوه في اللحظات الأخيرة
He's currently recuperating.
إنّه يتعافى حاليًّا من إصابته
Thank goodness! He's okay!
هذا مطمئن، إذًا هو بخير
He's been through a lot.
لقد عانى الأمرّين
Damn that Bege guy! I'll make him pay!
سحقًا، سأجعل بيجي يدفع الثمن غاليًا
Luffy, this is what I wanted to discuss with you.
لوفي، سأخبرك الآن بالجزئية الرئيسية
I came up with a plan after I learned everything from Pekoms.
خطرت لي خطة بعدما عرفت كل شيء من بيكومز
I tried to predict your actions.
فلقد كنتُ أفكر بماذا ستفعلون لو عرفتم؟
I figured that if you learned the truth,
وكنتُ واثقًا من أنّك عندما تعرف كل شيء
you would decide to rescue Sanji and his family.
ستقرر إنقاذ سانجي وعائلته
Perhaps it's not fair to Pekoms, but considering the circumstances,
...أشعر بالأسى على بيكومز، ولكن في ظل هذه الظروف
should we really make an enemy of Bege?
أترغب حقًّا بجعل بيجي عدوًّا لك؟
The tea party begins at 10 a.m.
حفلة الشاي ستبدأ في العاشرة صباحًا
That's about five hours from now.
أي بعد خمس ساعات من الآن
The 10 of us need to come up with a plan in that time frame.
...بخلافنا نحن العشرة الذين لا نملك خطة بعد
Stop counting us as a part of this!
كفّ عن احتسابنا معكم
You damn brutes! I'll let them know what you're up to!
سأخبرهم بما تخططون أيها الأوغاد
Listen, Luffy, Bege and his crew have been relentlessly preparing for this day.
اسمع يا لوفي، إنّ بيجي وطاقمه كرّسوا أنفسهم من أجل الاستعداد لهذا اليوم
Luffy! Sanji!
لوفي وسانجي
Let's ally with Bege!
دعونا ننضم لبيجي
What?!
ماذا؟
But... you're probably right.
لكنّك مُحق فعلًا
Hey, are you insane, Luffy?!
هل جُننت يا لوفي؟
Luffy wants to do this?!
أتتفق معه حقًّا يا لوفي؟
You see? I told you he would want to!
أرأيتم؟ كما أخبرتكم تمامًا
Luffy, four of our six here are against this!
أربعة منا نحن الستة غير موافقين على هذه الخطة يا لوفي
Don't you care about Bege-san's ill deeds?!
ألم تسمع ما قيل عن جرائم بيجي-سان؟
Well, this way, everything'll work out, right?
ولكن ألن يسير كل شيء على ما يرام بهذه الطريقة؟
You can't make a decision like that...
قرار كهذا لا يُتّخذ بهذه الطريقة
Actually, I arranged a meeting earlier. Do you want to go meet them?
في الحقيقة، لقد رتّبتُ كل شيء، فهل تريد مقابلتهم؟
Okay, let's go right now!
أجل، لنقابله حالًا
What?!
ماذا؟
Don't worry. If something doesn't feel right, you can refuse!
لا تقلقوا، يمكنكم رفض التعاون معهم إن لم يعجبكم العرض الذي سيقدمونه
We have a different goal, after all.
فهدفنا مختلف قليلًا عما يسعون له
Luffy, Sanji! Bege and his crew's base is on the northwest side of the island.
لوفي وسانجي، مقر بيجي وعشيرته يقع شمال غربيّ الجزيرة
The eight of us will head there first from this dimension. See you there!
ثمانيتُنا سنذهب إلى هناك من خلال المرايا، نراكم هناك
Stop counting us as part of your group!
أخبرتك ألّا تعدّنا بينكم
Okay, got it!
حسنًا، اتفقنا
Did you get rid of Bobbin?
هل أنهيتَ أمر بوبين؟
That's right, he was chasing Black Leg.
أجل، لقد كان يطارد الساق السوداء
I told you, Germa are my heroes.
الجيرما هم أبطالي على كل حال
Are they really coming here?
هل سيأتون حقًّا
Father?
يا فاذر؟
Jinbe isn't the type of man to joke around.
جينبي ليس الرجل الذي يمزح بمثل هذه الأمور
Since we're both opposing Big Mom,
«بما أنّ كلينا يسعى خلف بيغ مام»
we shouldn't make extra enemies— he's right about that.
«فينبغي أن نضع عداوتنا جانبًا» كان محقًّا حين قال هذا
Everything after that depends on what Straw Hat says.
الأمر يتوقف الآن على ما سيقوله قبعة القش
If it doesn't work out...
...إذا لم يرُق لنا كلامه
we'll just kill him!
سنقتله هنا
♪ Soft and fluffy... ♪
♪ طريّة ورقيقة ♪
♪ Moist and fluffy... ♪
♪ نديّة ورقيقة ♪
♪ ...life! ♪
♪ هذه الحياة ♪
♪ There's no such thing! ♪
♪ ليس هناك أحلى منها ♪
♪ A life of torment, the taste of tears... ♪
♪ مليئة بالعذاب، وطعم الدموع ♪
♪ A pinch of salt! ♪
♪ قدرٌ من المِلح ♪
♪ Tears of mortification! ♪
♪ دموع الأسى ♪
♪ A tablespoonful ♪
♪ ملء ملعقة ♪
♪ If that's how it is at least for your dessert... ♪
♪ إذا كانت حياتك كذلك ♪
♪ ...don't you want some sweet cake? ♪
♪ فما رأيك في شيء حلو؟ ♪
Head Chef! Head Chef!
رئيس الطهاة رئيس الطهاة
♪ Soft and fluffy... ♪
♪ طريّة ورقيقة ♪
♪ Moist and fluffy... ♪
♪ نديّة ورقيقة ♪
No, Pekoms! You need to rest!
توقف يا بيكومز، لا زلت تحتاج إلى الراحة
Did Jinbe really tell Mama about that rat, Bege?
هل قام جينبي بإبلاغ ماما عن ذلك الوغد بيجي؟
Of course!
بالطبع
By now, I'm guessing that Bege has been beaten to death by Mama.
أظن أنّ ماما تعاقبه الآن بشدة جزاء خيانته
You guess?! Your guess isn't enough! I gotta make sure to tell her...
تظن؟ ظنك لا يكفي، لا بدّ أن أتأكد من ذلك بنفسي
Whoa now!
هوّن عليك
You need to keep resting, Pekoms.
ما زلتَ تحتاج إلى الراحة يا بيكومز
But, Praline, in case they stop him from telling her...
...لكن يا برالين، إذا استطاعوا منعه من إخبارها
If you're concerned about that, then leaving it to Jinbe is the best option!
إن كان هذا ما يثير قلقك، فحريّ بك أن تثق بجينبي
You'll be beaten again in your current condition. Just keep quiet!
لن يكون بمقدورك فعل شيء وأنت بهذه الحالة، لذا ابقَ هادئًا وحسب
He's right, Pekoms! As a ship's doctor, I won't allow you to go!
إنّه محق يا بيكومز، وأنا طبيب السفينة لن أسمح لك بالمغادرة
Don't move a muscle!
لا تحاول النهوض
He's right! He's right!
إنّه مُحق، إنّه مُحق
– Yeah. – Rest! Rest!
أجل - استرح، استرح -
You guys are acting weird.
أنتم تتصرفون بغرابة يا رفاق
There was something going on last night in the inlet.
هناك أمرٌ ما كان يجري طيلة الليلة في الخليج
I saw some people carrying things around!
رأيت أناسًا يحملون أشياءً ما
I appreciate that you saved me, but I need to leave!
أشكركم على إنقاذي، ولكن ينبغي أن أذهب
Wait, wait, we can't allow that!
مهلًا مهلًا، أنا أمنعك من المغادرة
What do you mean you "can't"?
ما الذي تقصده بأمنعك-غاو؟
What are you guys hiding?!
ماذا تخفون عني؟
This is it!
وصلنا
This is Bege's base!
هذا هو مقر بيجي
So, what kind of guy is Bege?
إذًا، أي نوع من الرجال يكون؟
You heard what Jinbe said.
لقد سمعت ما قاله جينبي
You coward!
أيها الجبان
Think of him as a scheming and brutal mafia boss.
زعيم إحدى عصابات المافيا
My hero! Vinsmoke Sanji of Germa!
بطلي المفضل، أحد أفراد جيرما; فينسموك سانجي
I'm so happy to see you again-rero !
إني سعيد للغاية برؤيتك مجدّدًا-ريرو
It's you...
...إنّه أنت
Hey, where's everyone else? Are you Bege?
أنت، أين الآخرون؟ هل أنت بيجي؟
Don't be in such a rush. They are here or rero.
لا تكن عجولًا، جميعهم هنا أو-ريرو
What do you mean by "rero "?!
ما الذي تقصده بـ«ريرو»؟
Oh, Luffy! Sanji!
لوفي، سانجي
Sanji!
سانجي
You made me worried, you bastard!
لقد أقلقتني عليك أيها الوغد
I'm sorry for that... Hm?
أعتذر منكم
That aside, why are you dressed like this?
ولكن، لماذا تبدو هكذا؟
Why don't you guys go take a bath too?
ما رأيكم أن تستحمّوا أوّلًا؟
Why are you so relaxed?! We don't have time! And you don't even like baths!
لماذا أنت هاديء الأعصاب هكذا؟ ليس لدينا وقت للاسترخاء، كما أنّك لا تحب الاستحمام أصلًا
No, you two must take one, too-rero.
لا، يجب عليكما أن تستحمّا أولًا-ريرو
We'll talk afterwards-rero.
ثم سنتحدث بعد ذلك
A bath right now?!
حمّام ونحن في هذه الظروف؟
Father won't meet with anyone who is dirty.
فاذر لا يقابل أحدًا متسخًا هكذا
Who's dirty?!
متسخًا؟
What?! Lola was turned into a warthog zombie?!
ماذا؟ لولا تحولت إلى زومبي على هيئة خنزير؟
And she was chasing around a guy she fell in love with!
وكانت تطارد فارس أحلامها أيضًا
That definitely sounds like Lola!
هكذا هي دائمًا
Back then... and now once again in those scary woods,
عندما كنا مع تلك الشجرة في غابة الإغواء
I don't know what would've happened to me if it weren't for Lola.
لا أعرف ما كان سيحدث لنا لو لم ألتق بلولا
I see! But you guys saved my sister, too! Thank you!
هكذا إذًا، لكنكم أنقذتموها كذلك، شكرًا لكم
Oh, I'm crying tears of joy.
أنا أبكي من فرط السعادة
We've been close our entire lives.
...لقد كنا مقربتين من بعضنا جدًّا حينما كنا أطفالًا
Since we're twins!
لأنّنا توأم
A zombie! I can't imagine a dead person moving. The sea is like a wonderland!
زومبي؟ لا يمكنني تخيل جسد ميّت يتحرك كالأحياء البحر مليء بالعجائب
So, was Lola turned back into a human?
وهل تمكنت لولا من العودة إلى هيئتها البشرية بعد ذلك؟
That's right. I'm sure she's still doing well as a pirate.
أجل، أنا على يقين أنّها أصبحت قرصانة قوية
I wonder if she found someone to marry...
هل وجدت من تتزوجه يا تُرى؟
Big Mom sounded so mad when she talked about Lola running away from a marriage.
لقد بدت بيغ مام غاضبة للغاية حين تحدثت عن هرب لولا من زواجها
Yeah... that was a big deal.
أجل، لقد كانت أزمة كبيرة
What?
ماذا؟
Mama is reviled by all giants in the world for a reason.
جميع العمالقة في العالم يكرهون ماما لسببٍ ما
All of the giants in the world?
جميع العمالقة في العالم؟
That's why even though Totto Land has a diverse population,
...رغم تنوّع الأجناس في توتولاند
there are no giants.
إلّا أنّ العمالقة هو الجنس الوحيد الغير موجود
Giants really exist!
العمالقة موجودون حقًّا
One day,
...ذات يوم
Lola had a surprise suitor
ادّعى أحدهم أنّه وقع في غرام لولا من أول نظرة، وطلب الزواج منها
It was none other than Prince Loki of Elbaf, the land of the giants!
وكان هذا الرجل أمير أرض العمالقة إلباف; لوكي
A prince?! Amazing!
أمير؟ مذهل
Mama practically cried with joy.
فرحت ماما بهذا فرحًا شديدًا
She thought if Lola became the princess of Elbaf,
...لأنّه بمجرّد أن تصبح ابنتها لولا أميرة إلباف
her long-standing feud with the giants would be resolved,
فإنّ العداوة التي بينها وبين العمالقة ستنتهي
and she'd even gain access to the army of Elbaf, the country known as the mightiest in the whole world.
كما أنّ جيش العمالقة الذي يُعتبر أقوى جيش في العالم سيكون تحت طوعها
I see...
هكذا إذًا
So that's what she ran away from.
لكن ابنتها هربت
It all went downhill from there.
ثم تغيّر كل شيء بعد ذلك للأسوأ
She tried to use me as a substitute,
حاولت خداعه وقدّمتني له
but he noticed that I wasn't Lola.
لكنّه أدرك أنني لستُ لولا
So her relationship with the giants got even worse.
فساءت العلاقة بينها وبين العمالقة أكثر
Then, she gave up the idea of becoming friendly with actual giants
ثمّ تخلّت عن فكرة التحالف مع العمالقة الحقيقيين
and started investing in research to gigantify regular humans instead.
وبدأت بتمويل أبحاث تهدف لتحويل البشر العاديين إلى عمالقة
Her anger toward Lola only worsened, and she was branded a criminal in this country!
لكن غضبها من لولا ظل يكبر مع الأيام حتّى اعتُبرت مجرمة في أنحاء هذه الدولة
If she ever comes back, she'll be killed!
سيقتلونها إن عادت
Furthermore, she couldn't stand looking at me anymore, since I look just like Lola.
كما أنّها لم تكن تطيق النظر إليّ، لأني أُذكّرها بأختي لولا
Get that damn face out of my sight!
إيّاكِ أن تظهري بهذا الوجه أمامي أبدًا
When she saw me, she hit me without mercy. For years, I always had fresh wounds.
في كل مرة تراني فيها، تضربني بلا رحمة تعرّضتُ لإصابات شديدة استغرقت سنوات حتّى شُفيت منها
I was afraid that my own mother would kill me!
حتّى ظننتُ بأنني سأُقتل يومًا ما على يدي أمي
I can't see that monster as my mother anymore!
أصبحتُ لا أعتبرها أمي، بل كائن مسخ يهدد حياتي
However, Lola is very carefree... She probably has no idea that her mother wants to kill her.
لكن أختي لولا لطالما كانت فتاة طيبة القلب لذا لا أظنها تتصور أنّ أمها تنوي قتلها حقًّا
I see... Everything makes sense now.
هكذا إذًا، لقد اتضحت الأمور الآن
So when Bege said he was going to assassinate Mama, I felt nothing at all.
لهذا السبب لم أشعر بأي شيء عندما أخبرني بيجي أنّه يسعى لقتل ماما
You might think I'm terrible, but it's the truth.
قد تظنان بأني فتاة فظيعة، ولكن هذه هي الحقيقة
Well, well, that bath felt so good!
لقد كان حمامًا جيّدًا
Ah, just like heaven!
إنّها الجنة، الجنة
No, I refuse to move on to the next life!
لا أريد الخروج من هنا
This feels like the aftermath of a battle... I'm getting too relaxed. It hasn't even started yet!
نحن لم ننهِ شيئًا بعد، لا يمكننا الاسترخاء، ما يزال أمامنا قتال طويل
Luffy-san, Luffy-san.
لوفي-سان، لوفي-سان
There's milk in here. Milk!
لقد وجدت حليبًا هنا
Hey, don't go through our fridge without asking!
أنت، لا تفتح ثلاجتنا إلا بعد أن تستأذن
That's exactly what I needed. I lost my tooth.
هذا ما كنتُ أحتاجه تمامًا، لقد كُسِر سنّي
And my face has been cracked.
وأنا خُدش وجهي
Thank you for the milk!
شكرًا على الحليب
All better!
هذا أفضل
How is that even possible?!
كيف يُعقل هذا؟
I won't forgive you, Chiffon! I can't believe you!
لن أغفر لك يا شيفون، لا أستطيع تصديق ذلك
How can you help someone who wants to kill Mama!
كيف لكِ أن تكوني متواطئة مع شخص يسعى لاغتيال ماما؟
Mistress Chiffon, please think about this! You know no one could ever kill Mama!
أعيدي التفكير رجاءً يا شيفون-ساما فأنتِ تعلمين أنّ لا أحد يستطيع قتل ماما
Big Sis Brûlée!
أختي الكبرى بروليه
You know what she's done to me, right?
أنتِ تعرفين ما فعلته ماما بي، صحيح؟
I'm worried about Lola. Bege and Pez are my only family now!
لولا في خطر، وبيجي وبيز هما عائلتي الوحيدة
I don't need anyone else!
ولا أريد أحدًا سواهما
Oh, it's okay, it's okay.
لا بأس لا بأس
Okay, everyone's gathered, right?
حسنًا، الجميع هنا، أليس كذلك؟
Have you cleaned yourselves up a bit?
هل نظفتم أنفسكم جيّدًا؟
As the saying goes, "The suit makes the man."
يقولون أنّ الملابس تصنع الرجال
I won't talk to anyone that doesn't take care of their appearance.
لن أتعامل مع أناسٍ لا يهتمّون بمظهرهم
So, we've got three and a half hours to go.
والآن، أمامنا ثلاث ساعات ونصف
Let's first decide...
...لنحسم أولًا
if we're working together or not.
ما إذا كنا سنتحالف أو لا
They're good, aren't they, Luffy?
إنّه لذيذ يا لوفي
Why don't you guys restrain yourselves?!
أنتما كونا أكثر جدية
What? These are for us to eat, right?
ماذا؟ أتقصدين تناولنا لهذا الطعام؟
From our perspective, you guys are just a nuisance.
إنّكم مصدر قلق بالنسبة لنا
The easiest solution would be for us to kill all of you, here and now.
وقتلكم جميعًا هنا هو الحل الأمثل
Are you sure about that?
هل أنت واثق من ذلك؟
If I die, you won't have your chance to kill Big Mom.
إن مُت ستفقد فرصتك في قتل بيغ مام
Because the ceremony would be canceled.
لأنّه لن يكون هناك حفلة زفاف
If I'm not back two hours before the wedding, they'll be suspicious.
وإن لم أعد قبل الحفلة بساعتين على الأقل سيثير هذا الأمر شكوكهم
Yeah. I hate to admit it, but you're right.
أجل، للأسف أنت مُحق تمامًا
We'll keep you alive, in that case.
لا يمكنني قتلك أنت بالذات
We don't have time to waste on threats.
ليس لدينا وقت لنهدره بالتهديدات
Luffy, how are you feeling about this? Can you work with them?
ما الذي تشعر به بشأن التعاون معهم يا لوفي؟
What do you think?
ما رأيك؟
You're Caesar, aren't you?!
أنت سيزار، صحيح؟
What?! Caesar?! Where?!
ماذا؟ سيزار؟ أين هو؟
He's been here the whole time...
كان هنا طوال الوقت
How could you not notice...?
ألاحظتَه للتو؟
This research is so pointless! I'm not gonna work anymore!
لا فائدة من هذه الأبحاث، لن أعمل بعد الآن
Go ahead and do as you like with me, Big Mom!
سأخبر بيغ مام بذلك وليحدث ما يحدث
Caesar Clown!
سيزار كلاون
I-I-I'm working my butt off! Tell that to Big Mom!
إني أعمل بجد، أخبر بيغ مام بذلك
There's no need.
ليس هذا ما نحتاجه
What?
ماذا؟
When I asked them to let me watch over you, they agreed without a question.
عندما طلبت منهم مراقبتك وافقوا دون أي تردد
I'm now a trusted rook!
أنا الآن بمثابة قطعة القلعة الموثوق به
Is that my heart?!
أهذا قلبي؟
I'm willing to let you go. If you help me in return, that is...
سأخرجك من هنا إن تعاونت معنا
You bastard! Do you have any idea who you're talking to?!
أيها اللعين، ألا تعرف مع من تتحدّث؟
I'm the genius scientist Caesar Clown! I could destroy the world if I wanted to!
أنا العالم العبقري الذي بوسعه تدمير العالم؛ سيزار كلاون
I know who you are.
بل أعرف من أنت
That's why I came here.
لهذا السبب أتيت إليك
Damn!
سحقًا
I served Big Mom and now Bege!
أولًا بيغ مام، والآن بيجي
I gotta work anyway!
العمل يُلازمني في كل الحالات
Are you doing your job-rero ?
هل تقوم بعملك على أكمل وجه-ريرو؟
I am! Who do you think I am?!
بالطبع، مع من تظن نفسك تتحدث؟
This is much more to my liking than what she had me do!
هذا العمل أسهل لي من الآخر
The greatest piece of art will soon be completed!
سأنتهي من هذه التحفة الفنية قريبًا
That's good to know.
ينبغي أن تعرف
The Straw Hat crew will be here shortly-rero.
أنّ طاقم قبعة القش على وشك القدوم إلى هنا-ريرو
What?! The Straw Hats?!
ماذا؟ طاقم قبعة القش؟
Oh, come on! I never wanna see those guys again!
كلا، لا أودّ رؤيتهم مجدّدًا
When they're around, everything goes wrong!
إنّهم يُفسدون كل شيء يتدخلون فيه
Father wants you to attend the meeting too-rero.
الزعيم يريدك أن تحضر للاجتماع-ريرو
Don't be late.
لا تتأخر
I can't believe this!
لا يسعني تصديق ذلك
I've got no choice!
في هذه الحالة
C-Caesar? No, I am Bege's blood brother...
سـ-سيزار؟ كلا، أنا أخ بيجي
"Gangster" Gastino!
غانغستر» غاستينو»
He's not even attempting to hide it...
لم يبذل مجهودًا يُذكر لإخفاء هويته
"Gastino"?
غاستينو؟
Because he's a gas human?
هل لأنّه رجل غاز؟
He's even laughing the same way.
لم يغيّر ضحكته
I see.  I thought you were someone else. Sorry about that.
هكذا إذًا، ظننتك أحدٌ آخر. المعذرة
No, you were right! He's obviously Caesar!
كلا، أنت مُحق، إنّه سيزار بشحمه ولحمه
What?!
ماذا؟
Oh, so it is you! What are you doing here?!
إنّه أنت كما توقعت، ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Do you really think I'd be here if I had a choice, you idiot?!
أتظنني هنا بمحض إرادتي أيها الساذج؟
Because of you guys, I was handed over to Big Mom,
تمّ تسليمي لبيغ مام بسببكم أيها الأوغاد
and my only escape from certain death was this guy taking my heart and making me his slave!
والسبيل الوحيد لنجاتي هو الانصياع لأوامر هذا الرجل الذي بحوزته قلبي
I'm being pushed around!
لقد تمّ استغلالي
If you see Trafalgar Law, tell him I'll kill him when I see him again!
أخبروا ترافلغار لاو أنني سأقتله إن رأيتموه مجدّدًا
You too, if I get the chance!
وإن سنحت لي الفرصة سأقتلك أيضًا
Cut it out! This is so pointless.
اخرس، فهذا ممل
What a waste of time.
الوقت يُداهمنا
Straw Hat,
قبعة القش
are you going to work with me or not?
أتريد التعاون معنا أم لا؟
First of all, let me punch you for shooting Pekoms!
أولًا، سأجعلك تدفع ثمن إطلاق النار على بيكومز
Here I go!
ها أنا ذا
Stop it!
توقف
What?!
ماذا؟
Pull back your fist, Luffy! We won't come to an agreement this way!
اسحب قبضتك يا لوفي، فلا يمكننا التوصّل إلى اتفاق بهذه الطريقة
But he shot my friend!
لكنّه أطلق النار على صديقي
Anyone talking bad about Father is unforgivable!
لا يسعني تحمّل شخص يتحدّث بوقاحة مع فاذر
No, Gotti! Calm down-rero !
توقف يا غوتي، اهدأ
Cut it out!
توقف
I don't care. Let him do it.
لا أهتم، دعه يفعل ذلك
Kick these bastards out!
اطردوا هؤلاء الأوغاد
You back off!
تراجع أنت
Why?!
لماذا؟
I knew this would happen...
توقعت أنّ هذا ما سيحدث
Well, it can't be helped...
حسنًا، ما باليد حيلة
Do you like Big Mom?
هل تُحبّان بيغ مام؟
– No way!
كلا -
Then you're on the same side.
إذًا هذا يعني بأنّكم متفقين في أمر معيّن
Even if you don't share the same lifestyle or goals, you have a common enemy!
حتّى لو كنتم لا تتشاركون ذات الأسلوب أو الأهداف إلّا أنّكم تملكون ذات العدو الذي تريدون هزيمته
You can kill each other later,
يمكنكم قتل بعضكم لاحقًا
but if you join hands now, it'll be in everyone's favor!
ولكن إن تعاونتم الآن، فسيصب ذلك بصالح الجميع
So what's the plan?!
ما هي الخطة؟
I've planned the whole thing in exacting detail.
لقد أعددت خطة مثالية
Let's just do it! Then, I'll be through with you guys!
دعونا نطبقّها بسرعة، وبعدها سنحسم الأمور بيننا